<blog>
    <post>
        <date>December 1, 2022</date>
        <author>Ravi</author>
        <title>How to make Chicken Biryani</title>
        <summary>
            <image_path>https://myfoodstory.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/09/The-Best-Chicken-Biryani-Recipe-2.jpg</image_path>
            <text>How To Make Simple Chicken Biryani.</text>
        </summary>
        <body>
        Once you have your chicken marinated, rice and fried onions ready, start by cooking the marinated chicken. To cook the chicken, place it in the dutch oven or a large pot that you plan to use for cooking the biryani, and cook them for 7 minutes. There is no need to stir the chicken, only flip it once around the 4 minute mark.
        Once the chicken is partially cooked, the next step is to layer it with the fried onions, mint and coriander. The onions add sweetness and richness while the herbs add a ton of flavor and freshness.
        The final step is layering with 70% cooked basmati rice. Sprinkle saffron milk and ghee on top and cover tightly with a lid. Originally, the pot was sealed with dough to prevent steam from escaping, but a tight lid works just as well. It's important to cook this on a low flame so that the heat distributes evenly and the bottom doesn't get burnt.
        And there you go! The whole thing takes approximately an hour so I call this a weekend project, but after you've done it once, you'll realize how easy and simple making biryani at home is!
        </body>
    </post>    
    <post>
        <date>December 1, 2022</date>
        <author>Ravi</author>
        <title>Cristiano Ronaldo Named The GOAT</title>
        <summary>
             <image_path>https://media.bleacherreport.com/image/upload/x_172,y_77,w_1546,h_1028,c_crop/w_800,h_533,c_fill/v1669311902/ptvxlclmahlcueyirhge.jpg</image_path>
            <text>Cristiano Ronaldo was named as The GOAT After The Win vs Ghana</text>
             </summary>
             <body>
              Cristiano Ronaldo made history Thursday at the 2022 FIFA World Cup in Qatar, becoming the first male player to score at five different World Cups in a 3-2 opening win for Portugal over Ghana.
              The 37-year-old was tripped in the box for a penalty in the 65th minute, and he put Portugal ahead 1-0 from the spot
              "Cristiano is a magnificent player, but as a goalscorer,"Spanish football writer Juanma Trueba said. "I don't think he has the influence that other players through history like Pele, Maradona, Di Stefano had with the rest of the team. They helped their teams to become better. Cristiano needs to have that influence. He is more preoccupied with his game than worried about [his team's].
             </body>
    </post>
    <post>
        <date>December 1, 2022</date>
		<author>Rohit</author>
		<title>Josh Allen Named NFL's Scariest Player</title>
        <summary>
            <image_path>https://people.com/thmb/1HAL8vrV5dNIf1kcctltFYHYMGg=/750x0/filters:no_upscale():max_bytes(150000):strip_icc():focal(979x265:981x267):format(webp)/josh-allen-buffalo-bills-120122-53e3b5e302e74e019091fbe87af68d8a.jpg</image_path>
            <text>Buffalo Bills quarterback Josh Allen is currently the MVP favorite at +700 odds, according to FanDuel.</text>
		</summary>
        <body>
        It's no secret that there are high expectations for Buffalo Bills quarterback Josh Allen going into the season. Heck, his entire team has high expectations as they are pinned as the Super Bowl favorites.
        In a recent article by ESPN, which surveyed 50 NFL executives, Allen was ranked the third best quarterback behind the Green Bay Packers Aaron Rogers and the Kansas City Chiefs Patrick Mahomes. He was one spot in front of Tom Brady of the Tampa Bay Buccaneers.
        ESPN writer Field Yates explained: “I truly believe there is not a single player that is scarier to defend in the NFL than Josh Allen. … At his apex, I believe Josh Allen can be as dominant a player in the NFL as any other in the NFL this year. I am picking him as my MVP. …”
        Last season, Allen threw for 4407 yards, 36 touchdowns and 15 interceptions, leading the Bills to the AFC Divisional round. In the Bill's final game of the season, a 42-36 overtime loss to the Chiefs, which Yates said Allen played "arguably a prefect game of football," Allen went 27-for-37 for 329 yards and four touchdowns, all to receiver Gabriel Davis. Allen threw no interceptions and also added 68 rushing yards.
        The praise that Yates showed Allen isn't necessarily a super hot take. According to FanDuel, Allen is the MVP favorite at +700 odds, in front of Mahomes (+800), Brady (+800), Rogers (+1000) and the Chargers' Justin Herbert (+1000).
        Nonetheless, Yates went to bat for Allen, who will start his perhaps MVP campaign on Sept. 8 as the Bills take on the defending Super Bowl champion Los Angeles Rams. … another team featuring some “scary” talent.
        </body>
    </post>
</blog>